1 | P a g e

TERMS OF SERVICE (“ToS”)

THE FOLLOWING TERMS AND CONDITIONS (hereinafter the “Terms of Service” OR “ToS”) WILL BE LEGALLY

BINDING UPON YOU (hereinafter “You” or “Your”) IF YOU CHOOSE TO CONTINUE BEYOND THIS SCREEN TO

SEEK TELEMEDICINE MEDICAL CARE FROM THE INDEPENDENT MEDICAL PROVIDERS PROVIDING MEDICAL

SERVICES THROUGH THE MYIDEALDOCTOR NETWORK (the “MyIdealDOCTOR Network”), WHICH IS

MAINTAINED AND OPERATED BY MYIDEALDOCTOR, LLC OR ANY OF ITS AFFILIATES OR SUBSIDIARIES

(hereinafter “MyIdealDOCTOR,” “Our,” “Us” or “We”). TO THE EXTENT THAT THERE ARE CAPITALIZED TERMS

OR PHRASES USED HEREIN WHICH ARE NOT OTHERWISE DEFINED BELOW, PLEASE REFER TO THE

DEFINITIONS MAINTAINED AT https://myidealdoctor.com/agreements/

1.0 INTRODUCTORY TERMS

You acknowledge and agree that these Terms of Service, together with Our Informed Consent and Privacy Policy,

shall govern Your access to and use of the Services. Any conflicts between these Terms of Service and Our

Informed Consent and Privacy Policy shall be controlled first by the language contained within these Terms of

Service.

1.01 | Accuracy of Contact Information. At all times that You seek Services from the MyIdealDOCTOR

Network You shall provide accurate, current and complete about Your legal name, address, email address, and

phone number (the “Contact Information”), and maintain and promptly update the Contact information if any

of the Contact Information should change.

1.02 | User Names: Passwords, Access and Notification. You cannot share Your login rights to the

MyIdealDOCTOR Platform with any other individual, unless that Individual is accessing the MyIdealDOCTOR

Network with Your express permission and for Your benefit. You shall use reasonable efforts to prevent

unauthorized access to or use of the MyIdealDOCTOR Platform or Services and shall promptly notify Us of any

unauthorized access to or use of the MyIdealDOCTOR Platform or Services, as well as of any loss, theft or

unauthorized use of the User Name and/or Password associated with You and Your use of the MyIdealDOCTOR

Platform.

1.03 | General Restrictions. You promise that You will not send any Electronic Communication from or

through the MyIdealDOCTOR Platform that is unlawful, harassing, libelous, defamatory or threatening. You

promise that You will be responsible for all activities conducted under Your User Name and Password. You

promise that You will not access or use the MyIdealDOCTOR Platform: (i) to circumvent or exceed account

limitations or requirements of the Services; or, (ii) to obtain unauthorized access to the MyIdealDOCTOR

Platform (including without limitation permitting access to or use of the Services via another system or tool); or,

(c) in a manner that is contrary to applicable law or in violation of any third-party rights of privacy or intellectual

property rights; or, (iv) to publish, post, upload or otherwise transmit Customer Data that contains any viruses,

trojan horses, worms, time bombs, corrupted files or other computer programming routines that are intended

to damage, detrimentally interfere with, surreptitiously intercept or expropriate any systems, data, personal

2 | P a g e

information or property of another, including, but not limited to the MyIdealDOCTOR Platform. You shall comply

with all applicable local, state, federal, and foreign laws, treaties, regulations, and conventions in connection

with Your use of the MyIdealDOCTOR Platform or Services, including without limitation, those related to privacy,

electronic communications and anti-spam legislation. You agree not to access the MyIdealDOCTOR Platform by

any means other than through the interfaces that We provide to You.

1.04 | Third-Party Application(s). We may offer Third-Party Applications for use directly within the

MyIdealDOCTOR Platform in conjunction with the Services. We do not warrant, either expressly or implicitly,

any Third-Party Applications, and any use of a Third-Party Application is Your risk to bear.

1.05 | Data Security. We shall maintain commercially reasonable administrative, physical and technical

safeguards designed for the protection, confidentiality and integrity of Your Data as further described within

Our Informed Consent and Privacy Policy.

1.06 | Confidentiality. We agree to use the same degree of care that We use to protect the confidentiality

of Our own Confidential Information of like kind (at all times exercising a reasonable degree of care in the

protection of such Confidential Information) not to use or disclose Your Confidential Information except to the

extent necessary to perform its obligations or exercise rights under any Agreement or as directed by law.

However, in the even that You input Confidential Information such as credit card information or social security

numbers in fields within the MyIdealDOCTOR Platform which are not otherwise designated for such data, We

cannot assure the protection of this information, and You agree and acknowledge that any representations by

Us about the confidentiality or security of this data are rendered null and void. Nothing in these Terms of

Service will prohibit the disclosure of Confidential Information to the extent that such disclosure is required by

law or regulation, order of a court or other governmental authority or regulation, or at Our reasonable

discretion upon advice of Our legal counsel.

1.07 | Ownership of Your Data. All title and intellectual property rights in and to the Your Patient Data

is owned exclusively by You, subject to the terms of the Informed Consent and Privacy Policy.

1.08 | Our Intellectual Property Rights. All rights, title and interest in and to the MyIdealDOCTOR Platform

or the Services provided in conjunction therewith (including without limitation all intellectual property rights

therein and all modifications, extensions, customizations, scripts or other derivative works of the

MyIdealDOCTOR Platform provided or developed by Us) are owned exclusively by Us or Our licensors. The

rights granted to You herein do not convey any ownership rights in the MyIdealDOCTOR Platform, express or

implied, or ownership in any of the Services, or any intellectual property rights thereto. Our service marks,

logos and product and service names (hereinafter, the "MyIdealDOCTOR Marks") are Our property. You are

not permitted to use the MyIdealDOCTOR Marks without the prior written consent of Our authorized

representative.

1.09 | Dispute Resolution. You agree to maintain the confidential nature of all disputes and

disagreements that You may have with Us, including, but not limited to, informal negotiations, mediation

3 | P a g e

or arbitration, except as may be necessary to prepare for or conduct these dispute resolution procedures

or unless otherwise required by law or judicial decision. You agree that in the event that You have a dispute or

disagreement with Us, and before You seek mediation, arbitration, or any other form of legal relief, You

shall provide written notice (the “Notice,” which must be sent to Us by email to legal@relymd.com) to Us

setting forth specific details of Your complaint. Upon receipt of the Notice, We shall have the right to

schedule at least one (1) meeting (in person or by video- or tele-conference) for the purpose of attempting in

good faith to resolve Your complaint. Any and all disputes, claims or controversies arising out of or relating to

these Terms of Service or Our Informed Consent and Privacy Policy shall be submitted to JAMS (formerly known

as the “Judicial Arbitration and Mediation Services, Inc.”) for mediation before arbitration or any other form

of legal relief may be instituted. Mediation may be commenced by Our providing JAMS a written request for

mediation setting forth the subject of the dispute and the relief requested. You agree to cooperate with JAMS

in selecting a single mediator and scheduling a mediation, which should take place within forty-five (45) days

following Our receipt of the Notice. You agree that You will participate in the mediation in good faith and share

equally in its costs. The mediation shall take place either in Durham, North Carolina, or at a forum located in

Durham County, North Carolina.

2.0 | DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES

WE DO NOT REPRESENT THAT YOUR USE OF THE MYIDEALDOCTOR PLATFORM WILL BE SECURE, TIMELY,

UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE, THAT THE MYIDEALDOCTOR PLATFORM OR SERVICES WILL MEET YOUR

REQUIREMENTS, OR THAT ALL ERRORS IN THE MYIDEALDOCTOR PLATFORM AND/OR DOCUMENTATION

RELATED THERETO, IF ANY, WILL BE CORRECTED OR THAT THE OVERALL SYSTEM THAT MAKES THE

MYIDEALDOCTOR PLATFORM AVAILABLE (INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE INTERNET, OTHER

TRANSMISSION NETWORKS, OR ANY LOCAL NETWORK AND EQUIPMENT) WILL BE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER

HARMFUL COMPONENTS. THERE ARE NO OTHER WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED,

INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, THOSE OF MERCHANTABILITY, SATISFACTORY QUALITY, FITNESS FOR A

PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR NON-INFRINGEMENT OF THIRD-PARTY RIGHTS. THE MYIDEALDOCTOR PLATFORM

IS PROVIDED TO YOU ON AN “AS-IS/WHERE-IS” AND “AS-AVAILABLE” BASIS. WE EXPRESSLY DISCLAIM ANY

REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES NOT OTHERWISE SET FORTH HEREIN, IF ANY. YOU ASSUME ALL

RESPONSIBILITY FOR DETERMINING WHETHER THE MYIDEALDOCTOR PLATFORM, THE INFORMATION

GENERATED THEREBY OR THROUGH THE USE THEREOF IS, OR THE SERVICES PROVIDED THEREUPON ARE,

ACCURATE OR SUFFICIENT FOR YOUR PURPOSES.

3.0 | LIMITATIONS OF LIABILITY

TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT SHALL WE BE LIABLE TO ANY PARTY FOR LOST

PROFITS OR REVENUE OR FOR INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, PUNITIVE, COVER, SPECIAL, RELIANCE OR

EXEMPLARY DAMAGES, OR INDIRECT DAMAGES OF ANY TYPE OR KIND HOWEVER CAUSED, WHETHER FROM

BREACH OF WARRANTY, BREACH OR REPUDIATION OF CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE, OR ANY OTHER LEGAL

CAUSE OF ACTION FROM OR IN CONNECTION WITH THESE TERMS OF SERVICE, THE INFORMED CONSENT AND

PRIVACY NOTICE, AND/OR ANY OTHER IMPLIED OR EXPRESS AGREEMENT (WHETHER OR NOT WE HAVE BEEN

4 | P a g e

ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES). CERTAIN STATES AND/OR JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW

THE EXCLUSION OF INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, IN WHICH CASE SUCH DAMAGES SHALL BE

SUBJECT TO THE LIMITATIONS SET FORTH IN THE FOLLOWING PARAGRAPH.

OUR MAXIMUM LIABILITY ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH ANY AGREEMENT OR ANY LICENSE,

USE OR OTHER D E PLOYMENT OF THE MYIDEALDOCTOR PLATFORM OR ANY SERVICES, WHETHER SUCH

LIABILITY ARISES FROM ANY CLAIM BASED ON BREACH OR REPUDIATION OF CONTRACT, BREACH OF

CONFIDENTIALITY, BREACH OF WARRANTY, NEGLIGENCE, TORT, STATUTORY DUTY, OR OTHERWISE, SHALL BE

NO GREATER ONE THOUSAND DOLLARS ($1,000). NOTWITHSTANDING THE PREVIOUS SENTENCE, WE SHALL

NOT BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY OTHER PARTY TO THE EXTENT SUCH LIABILITY WOULD NOT HAVE OCCURRED

BUT FOR YOUR OR THE OTHER PARTY’S FAILURE TO COMPLY WITH THESE TERMS OF SERVICE, WITH THE

TERMS OF THE INFORMED CONSENT AND PRIVACY NOTICE, OR WITH THE TERMS OF ANY OTHER IMPLIED OR

EXPRESS AGREEMENT.

4.0 | INDEMNIFICATION You shall not be entitled to indemnification by Us under any circumstance.

5.0 | INSURANCE We will maintain such insurance coverage as is reasonably necessary to support Our

obligations hereunder.

6.0 | CHANGE TO TERMS OF SERVICE. If We make a material change to these Terms of Service, or to

any related URL Terms, We will attempt to make a general announcement on Our website. If the change has a

material adverse impact on You and You do not agree to the change, You must so notify Us in writing via an

email sent to legal@relymd.com within ten (10) days after receiving notice of the change. If You access the

MyIdealDOCTOR Network or obtain Services after any change to these Terms of Service, You shall be deemed

to have consented to the revised Terms of Service

END OF THE TERMS OF SERVICE
